A Guide to the Joseph B. Benedetti Papers 1983-1997
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Series One, n.d. 1981-1993
  - Republican Caucus: questionaires 1984 (Box-folder 36.4)
  - Republican Convention 1993 (Box-folder 36.5)
  - Republican Party 1990 (Box-folder 36.6)
  - Republican Party: Chairman's race 1992 (Box-folder 36.7)
  - Republican Party: National 1982-85 (Box-folder 36.8)
  - Republican Party: National 1983-1984 (Box-folder 36.9)
  - Republican Party: Outreach, minorities 1982-1985 (Box-folder 36.10)
  - Republican Party: Political Action Committees, n.d. 1985 (Box-folder 37.1)
  - Republican Party: Richmond, n.d. 1983-1985 (Box-folder 37.2)
  - Republican Party: State Central Committee 1984 (Box-folder 37.3)
  - Republican Party: Virginia 1983-1984, 1986 (Box-folder 37.4)
  - Republican Party: Virginia Legislature 1983-1984 (Box-folder 37.5)
  - Republican Plan: Tax Windfall 1989 (Box-folder 37.6)
  - Republican Women, Virginia Federation 1982-1983 (Box-folder 37.7)
  - Respiratory Therapy 1980-1982 (Box-folder 37.8)
  - Restrictive Covenants for Group Homes (H.B. 207) 1982-1986 (Box-folder 37.9)
  - Retail Gasoline Dealers (Box-folder 38.1)
  - Retirees Tax Bill 1989 (Box-folder 38.2)
  - Revisions of Standards of Quality 1989 (Box-folder 38.3)
  - Revocation of License 1990 (Box-folder 38.4)
  - RF and P Corporation State Stock Holdings 1990 (Box-folder 38.5)
  - Richmond Area Business Group on Health 1985-1986 (Box-folder 38.6)
  - Richmond Child Care Commission 1988 (Box-folder 38.7)
  - Richmond: Central Richmond Association 1982-1985 (Box-folder 38.8)
  - Richmond, City of 1990 (Box-folder 38.9)
  - Richmond: City Code 1985 (Box-folder 38.10)
  - Richmond: City Council Legislative Committee 1982-1985 (Box-folder 38.11)
  - Richmond: City Water Works 1989 (Box-folder 38.12)
  - Richmond: Community Services Board 1983-1985 (Box-folder 38.13)
  - Richmond Dental Society 1982-1985 (Box-folder 38.14)
  - Richmond First Club: Report on Metropolitan Cooperation 1982 (Box-folder 38.15)
  - Richmond: Initiative (Black on Black Crime) 1991 (Box-folder 38.16)
  - Richmond: James River 1983-1984 (Box-folder 39.1)
  - Richmond: James River (H.B. 360) 1984 (Box-folder 39.2)
  - Richmond: James River 1984-1986 (Box-folder 39.3)
  - Richmond: James River: Pipeline proposal 1984 (Box-folder 39.4)
  - Richmond: Legislative Package 1991 (Box-folder 39.5)
  - Richmond: Legislative positions 1986-1987 (Box-folder 39.6)
  - Richmond: Legislative program 1990 (Box-folder 39.7)
  - Richmond: Legislative proposals 1985-1987 (Box-folder 39.8)
  - Richmond: Mayor Roy A. West 1983-1985 (Box-folder 39.9)
  - Richmond: Metropolitan Chamber of Commerce 1982-1985 (Box-folder 40.1)
  - Richmond: miscellaneous 1984-1985 (Box-folder 40.2)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Commission 1984-1985 (Box-folder 40.3)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Commission: Solid Waste Task Force 1984 (Box-folder 40.4)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Commission: Water Resources Task Force 1985-1986 (Box-folder 40.5)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Legislative Agenda 1989, 1991 (Box-folder 40.6)
  - Richmond Regional Planning District Reports 1990 (Box-folder 40.7)
  - Richmond resolutions: homeless; mental health; drug abuse 1990 (Box-folder 40.8)
  - Richmond School Board 1987 (Box-folder 40.9)
  - Richmond School Board 1990 (Box-folder 40.10)
  - Richmond School Board Legislative Program 1990 (Box-folder 40.11)
  - Richmond Water Purification Facility 1988 (Box-folder 40.12)
  - Right of Appeal 1983, 1986 (Box-folder 40.13)
  - Right of Appeal 1990 (Box-folder 40.14)
  - Right to Work laws 1984 (Box-folder 40.15)
  - Rigsby, Elisabeth 1989 (Box-folder 40.16)
  - Riverton School Project 1991 (Box-folder 40.17)
  - Riverboat Gambling 1994 (Box-folder 40.18)
  - Riverfront Development Program (Box-folder 40.19)
  - Rolfe (J.) Parkway Study 1990 (Box-folder 41.1)
  - Roll Call votes 1984 (Box-folder 41.2)
  - Roll call votes 1985 (Box-folder 41.3)
  - Roll call votes 1986 (Box-folder 41.4)
  - Roll call votes 1987 (Box-folder 41.5)
  - Roll call votes 1988 (Box-folder 41.6)
  - Roll call votes 1989 (Box-folder 41.7)
  - Roll call votes 1990 (Box-folder 41.8)
  - Route 288 1988 (Box-folder 41.9)
  - Route 895 Connector 1989 (Box-folder 41.10)
  - Rules Committee 1993 (Box-folder 41.11)
  - Rules Committee, Joint: Study of Legislative Process HJR 13 1992 (Box-folder 41.12)
  - Save Oregon Hill 1990 (Box-folder 41.13)
  - Save Oregon Hill 1991 (Box-folder 41.14)
  - SCC Judgeship Elections 1992 (Box-folder 41.15)
  - School Boards; Elected 1989 (Box-folder 41.16)
  - School Funding: Henrico 1988 (Box-folder 41.17)
  - School Funding: Richmond 1989 (Box-folder 41.18)
  - Seat belts 1984-1985 (Box-folder 42.1)
  - Self Sufficiency Trusts 1989 (Box-folder 42.2)
  - Senate By-Laws 1988-1992 (Box-folder 42.3)
  - Senate Finance 1991 (Box-folder 42.4)
  - Senate Information 1992 (Box-folder 42.5)
  - Senate Memoranda 1991-1993 (Box-folder 42.6)
  - Senate Procedural Resolutions 1992 (Box-folder 42.7)
  - Senate Republican Caucus (2 folders) 1992-1995 (Box-folder 42.8)
  - Senate Republican Caucus: Charlottesville meeting 12/4/92 (Box-folder 43.1)
  - Senate Republican Caucus: Committee Assignments 1992 (Box-folder 43.2)
  - Senate Republican retreat 1992 (Box-folder 43.3)
  - Sewage Handling and Disposal Regulations 1983-1985 (Box-folder 43.4)
  - Shepherd Agency 1989 (Box-folder 43.5)
  - Shine the Loght 1992 (Box-folder 43.6)
  - Smoking Bills 1990 (Box-folder 43.7)
  - Social Security withdrawal 1982-1983 (Box-folder 43.8)
  - Social Services, Department of 1982-1985 (Box-folder 43.9)
  - Solid Waste 1988 (Box-folder 44.1)
  - Special Session, Senate 1986 (Box-folder 44.2)
  - Special Session, Senate 1986 (Box-folder 44.3)
  - Speech material, n.d. 1985 (Box-folder 44.4)
  - Speeches 1984-1985 (Box-folder 44.5)
  - Stadium--Redskins (2 folders) 1992 (Box-folder 44.6)
  - Stadium--Redskins: Correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 44.8)
  - Standard of Care HB 1077 1988 (Box-folder 45.1)
  - Standards of Quality 1991 (Box-folder 45.2)
  - Standards of Quality: Funding 1988 (Box-folder 45.3)
  - State aid to localities 1986 (Box-folder 45.4)
  - State aid to localities 1989-1990 (Box-folder 45.5)
  - State Corporation Commission 1982, 1984 (Box-folder 45.6)
  - State Employees' Health Care Plan (Key Advantage) 1992 (Box-folder 45.7)
  - State Grants Hisoric Preservation 1990 (Box-folder 45.8)
  - State Legislative Leaders' Foundation 1992 (Box-folder 45.9)
  - State Song 1988 (Box-folder 45.10)
  - Statues of Limitations and Accural of Causes of Action HJR 173 1993 (Box-folder 45.11)
  - Stolen property (S.B. 346) 1988 (Box-folder 45.12)
  - Surrogate Motherhood 1990 (Box-folder 45.13)
  - Surrogate Mothers 1988 (Box-folder 45.14)
  - Tax exemption: Old Time Gospel Hour (S. B. 468) 1987 (Box-folder 45.15)
  - Tax on drugs (H.B. 946) 1983-1988 (Box-folder 46.1)
  - Tax windfall (S.B. 422) 1987 (Box-folder 46.2)
  - Taxes 1982-1985 (Box-folder 46.3)
  - Teenage Pregnancy 1987 (Box-folder 46.4)
  - Telecommunications 1982-1984 (Box-folder 46.5)
  - Term Limits 1992 (Box-folder 47.1)
  - Terry, Mary Sue 1989-1990 (Box-folder 47.2)
  - Terry, Marry Sue 1993 (Box-folder 47.3)
  - Theatre VA 1992 (Box-folder 47.4)
  - Tobacco 1983-1984, 1986 (Box-folder 47.5)
  - Tort reform, bill summaries 1986-1987 (Box-folder 47.6)
  - Tourism, n.d. 1983-1984 (Box-folder 47.7)
  - Tours: Capitol Mansion 1982-1984 (Box-folder 47.8)
  - Towing industry, regulation of 1986 (Box-folder 47.9)
  - Training and Employment Programs in Va 1990 (Box-folder 47.10)
  - Transfer of Development Rights 1991 (Box-folder 47.11)
  - Transprotation Funding Session: legislative veto session 1986 (Box-folder 47.12)
  - Transportation: Governor's Commission on 1986 (Box-folder 47.13)
  - Transprotation: Governor's Commission on 1986 (Box-folder 47.14)
  - Tution Assistance Act 1982-1984 (Box-folder 47.15)
  - Turnpike Tolls (Box-folder 47.16)
  - Underground storage tanks--G.L. subcommittee 1985-1986 (Box-folder 47.17)
  - United to Serve America 1992 (Box-folder 47.18)
  - Unite Way 1982-1983 (Box-folder 48.1)
  - Urban Compact Richmond 1990 (Box-folder 48.2)
  - Uranium mining 1982-1985 (Box-folder 48.3)
  - Uranium mining 1982-1985 (Box-folder 48.4)
  - Vehicle Emissions Bill (Richmond) SB 961 1993 (Box-folder 49.1)
  - Vepco 1984 (Box-folder 49.2)
  - Veterans 1982-1985 (Box-folder 49.3)
  - Virginia Action 1984 (Box-folder 49.4)
  - Virginia Association of Chiefs of Police 1984 (Box-folder 49.5)
  - Virginia Association of Community Services Boards 1982-1983 (Box-folder 49.6)
  - Virginia Association of Counties 1982-1985 (Box-folder 49.7)
  - Virginia Automatic Merchandising Association 1982-1983 (Box-folder 49.8)
  - Virginia Citizens Concumer Council 1983-1985 (Box-folder 49.9)
  - Virginia Clean Indoor Act 1990 (Box-folder 49.10)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Center for Public Affairs 1986 (Box-folder 49.11)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Special Collections and Archives 1987-1989 (Box-folder 49.12)
  - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation 1982-1984 (Box-folder 49.13)
  - Virginia Gasoline and Automotive Repair Association 1984 (Box-folder 49.14)
  - Virginia Governmental Employees Association 1982-1986 (Box-folder 49.15)
  - Virginia Health Services Cost Review Council 1985 (Box-folder 49.16)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science 1984 (Box-folder 49.17)
  - Virginia Institiute for Scientific Research 1985-1986 (Box-folder 49.18)
  - Virginia Leadership Group 1992 (Box-folder 49.19)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association 1982-1983 (Box-folder 49.20)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association 1992 (Box-folder 49.21)
  - Virginia Military Institute 1992 (Box-folder 49.22)
  - Virginia Municipal League 1983-1986 (Box-folder 49.23)
  - Virginia Municipal League 1991 (Box-folder 50.1)
  - Virginia Museum 1985 (Box-folder 50.2)
  - Virginia National Guard 1991 (Box-folder 50.3)
  - Virginia Nurses' Associations 1982-1983 (Box-folder 50.4)
  - Virginia Optometrists 1983-1985 (Box-folder 50.5)
  - Virginia Parole Board 1983-1984 (Box-folder 50.6)
  - Virginia Pharmaceutical Association 1985-1986 (Box-folder 50.7)
  - Virginia Pilot Survey: Republican Caucus 1991 (Box-folder 50.8)
  - Virginia Restaurant Association, n.d. 1983 (Box-folder 50.9)
  - Virginia Retail Merchants Association 1983-1985 (Box-folder 50.10)
  - Virginia Retirement System 1992 (Box-folder 50.11)
  - Virginia Savings and Loan League 1983 (Box-folder 50.12)
  - Virginia School Law Changes 1990 (Box-folder 50.13)
  - Virginia State Board of Elections 1983-1984 (Box-folder 50.14)
  - Virginia State Library 1985-1986 (Box-folder 50.15)
  - Virginia State Sherriffs Association 1982-1983 (Box-folder 50.16)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System 1982-1985 (Box-folder 51.1)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System: District Court Personnel 1984 (Box-folder 51.2)
  - Virginia War Memorial Commission 1983-1985 (Box-folder 51.3)
  - Virginia Water Resources Research Center 1983-1985 (Box-folder 51.4)
  - Virginia Water Resources Research Center: Water News 1983-1985 (Box-folder 51.5)
  - Virginians for Intergrity in Government 1991 (Box-folder 51.6)
  - Waste Disposal 1991 (Box-folder 51.7)
  - Waste Management 1990 (Box-folder 51.8)
  - Waste Management 1991 (Box-folder 51.9)
  - Water 1981-1984 (Box-folder 51.10)
  - Water 1983-1985 (Box-folder 51.11)
  - Water Resources 1989 (Box-folder 52.1)
  - Welfare Fraud Prosecution 1989 (Box-folder 52.2)
  - Welfare Reform: Impact of U.S. Mandates 1988 (Box-folder 52.3)
  - Wetlands 1990 (Box-folder 52.4)
  - Wetlands 1993 (Box-folder 52.5)
  - Whitcomb, Wayne 1992 (Box-folder 52.6)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, Governor 1990 (Box-folder 52.7)
  - Williams, Earle 1991 (Box-folder 52.8)
  - Williams, Earle 1993 (Box-folder 52.9)
  - Windfall Tax SB 517 1989 (Box-folder 52.10)
  - Women's bills 1986 (Box-folder 52.11)
  - Workforce Transition Act 1995 (Box-folder 52.12)
  - YMCA Mock General Assembly 1991 (Box-folder 52.13)
  - Youth to Power 1993 (Box-folder 52.14)
- Series Two 1986-1997
  - Agee for Attorney General 1993 (Box 53)
  - Allen, George for Governor 1993 (Box 53)
  - Attorney General--Dennis Peterson 1993 (Box 53)
  - American Legislative Exchange Council (Box 53)
  - Bills and Summaries (JBB/Senate) 1990 (Box 53)
  - Bill Racking 1992-1995 (Box 53)
  - Blab T.V. 1990-1991 (Box 53)
  - Bond Issues 1992 (Box 53)
  - Bonds, Pledge (JBB/Senate) (Box 53)
  - Budget Oversight Committee (Box 53)
  - Campaign Ideas (Box 53)
  - Capital Area Assembly 1991 (Box 53)
  - Capital Representation Resource Center (Board of Directors) (Box 53)
  - Census 2000 JBB/Legislative (Box 53)
  - Campaign 1995 (Box 53)
  - Chief Patron Report through Session JBB/Senate 1991 (Box 53)
  - Fuels Subcommittee (Box 53)
  - Collection Agencies (SB995-1993/1994) (Box 53)
  - Courts of Justice: Judicial Interviews (Box 53)
  - Courts of Justice subcommittee SB255 and SB256 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - Crime and Violence by Students on school property 1992 (Box 53)
  - Dillon Rule (Box 53)
  - Drug Free Workplace Legislative subcommittee 1991 (Box 53)
  - Preservation Act Ecology Issues (Box 53)
  - Ethics Senate/JBB (Box 53)
  - Farris for Lt. Governor 1993 (Box 53)
  - Fish Passage Senate 1992 (Box 53)
  - General Obligation bond Senate 1992 (Box 53)
  - Gilmore for Attorney General 1993 (Box 53)
  - Governor's Commission on Ethics 1992-1993 (Box 53)
  - Gun Control Study Committee--Richmond City Council (Box 53)
  - Harper v. VA Dept. of Taxation (Fed) (Box 53)
  - Health Care Insurance (Senate/JBB) (Box 53)
  - Highway Funding Legislative/JBB (Box 53)
  - Intergovernmental Cooperation Commission on 1992 (Box 53)
  - Indian Head Division Association (Box 53)
  - Indigent Health Care Fund (Box 53)
  - Italian-American Society of Richmond (Box 53)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) (Box 53)
  - Knights of Columbus (Box 53)
  - Land Usage (Box 53)
  - Ladfill Use fee and Hydrant tax--Richmond HB 1393 (Box 53)
  - Literary Fund (Box 53)
  - Little Sisters of the Poor Board JBB (Box 53)
  - Va Lottery (Box 53)
  - Massions's Casinos (Box 53)
  - MAPS--political districts (Box 53)
  - Mathematics and Science Center Foundation (JBB Board member) (Box 53)
  - Miller for Governor 1993 (Box 53)
  - Minter, George (Box 53)
  - Nance, Thomas N. City of Richmond (Box 53)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures (Box 53)
  - North, Oliver (Box 53)
  - Outcome based Education (Box 53)
  - Page Applications 1994 (Box 53)
  - Page Applications 1995 (Box 53)
  - Page--Senate Applications (Box 53)
  - Page Senate Applications (Box 53)
  - Parental Leave (Box 53)
  - Partnership for Urban Virginia (Box 53)
  - Phillpot Leadership Committee (Box 53)
  - Police Athletic League JBB/Peronal (Box 53)
  - Possible Legislation 1993 (Box 53)
  - Postal Information (Box 53)
  - Preneed Funeral Contracts subcommittee (Box 53)
  - Prior, Gordon (Box 53)
  - Press Conference (Box 53)
  - Probation Office, district 1 JBB/Legislative (Box 53)
  - Privileges and Elections Committee--Law Changes (Box 53)
  - PRO-STAR JBB/misc. (Box 53)
  - Proprietary Child Care Association of VA (Box 53)
  - Questionaires 1995 (Box 53)
  - Questionaires (Box 53)
  - Senate Republican Caucus 1992 (Box 54)
  - Senate Republican Caucus C'ville meeting 1992 (Box 54)
  - VA Pilot Survey (Box 54)
  - Shine the Light 1992 (Box 54)
  - Conflicts--Partners and Assoc. MC and D 1988 (Box 54)
  - Conflict of Interest Statement (Box 54)
  - Shepherd Agency (Box 54)
  - SCC Judgeship Elections 1992 (Box 54)
  - Stadium--Redskin's 1992 (Box 54)
  - Stadium--Correspondence (Box 54)
  - State Employees' Health Care Plan Key Advantage 1992 (Box 54)
  - State Legislative Leaders' Foundation (Box 54)
  - Statutes of Limitation and Accural of Causes of Action HJR 173 (Box 54)
  - Term Limits 1992 (Box 54)
  - Terry, Mary Sue (Box 54)
  - Theatre Virginia (Box 54)
  - United to Serve America 1992 (Box 54)
  - Vehicle emissions Bill Richmond JBB's SB961 1993 (Box 54)
  - Virginia Leadership Group (Box 54)
  - Virginians for Integrity in Government (Box 54)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association (Box 54)
  - VCU Special Collections and Archives Dept. (Box 54)
  - VMI 1992 (Box 54)
  - Virginia National Guard (Box 54)
  - VA Retirement System ads. Mary Sue Terry (Box 54)
  - Wetlands (Box 54)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas Governor (Box 54)
  - Williams, Earle 1991 (Box 54)
  - Williams, Earle (Box 54)
  - Windfall Tax re SB517 (Box 54)
  - Workforce Transition Act (Box 54)
  - Youth to Power 1993 (Box 54)
  - YMCA Mock General Assembly (Box 54)
  - Cultural Laureate (Box 54)
  - Campaign 1995 (Box 54)
  - City of Richmond Legislative Program (Box 55)
  - Republican Caucus--policy committee (Box 55)
  - Republican Convention 1993 (Box 55)
  - RPV--Chairman's Race 1992 (Box 55)
  - Caucus Finance Committee-Special 1990 (Box 55)
  - Republican Caucus Fundraising 1988 (Box 55)
  - Joint Republican Caucus 1990 (Box 55)
  - Republican Caucus (Box 55)
  - Republican Caucus Campaign plan (Gresham) 1989 (Box 55)
  - Republican Caucus--Organization and Future Planning (Box 55)
  - Joint Republican Caucus--Wintergreen Resort 1992 (Box 55)
  - Republican Advance 1990 (Box 55)
  - Republican Advance 1989 (Box 55)
  - Republican Advance 1988 (Box 55)
  - Census Fact Sheets (Box 55)
  - Senate Republican Caucus (Box 55)
  - Sales Representatives Contract--Legislation 1993 (Box 55)
  - Rules Committee, Joing HJR13 (Study of Legislative Process) (Box 55)
  - Rules Committee (Box 55)
  - Riverboat Gambling (Box 55)
  - Riverfront Development Program (Box 55)
  - Riverton School Project (Box 55)
  - Legislative leftover work (Box 55)
  - Senate Session 1988 (Box 55)
  - Senate Information (Box 55)
  - Correspondence (Box 55)
  - Senate Memoranda (Box 55)
  - Senate Procedural Resolutions (Box 55)
  - Senate By-laws (Box 55)
  - Senate Republican Caucus (Box 55)
  - Senate Republican Caucus retreat 1992 (Box 55)
  - ABC-Hearing Procedures (SJ 89) 1989 (Box 56)
  - Abolition of Parole (SB 3001) 1994 (Box 56)
  - Abortion Bills 1994 (Box 56)
  - Abortion Laws/Study (SJ 90) 1987 (Box 56)
  - Abortions Viable Fetus (SB 669) 1988 (Box 56)
  - Accident Reports (SB 767) 1989 (Box 56)
  - Administration of the Gov't film office advisory board (SB 342) 1994 (Box 56)
  - AFDC and Workforce Transition 1995 (Box 56)
  - Amending Rules of Senate (SR 5) 1992-1993 (Box 56)
  - Amendment-extending session defeated (HJR 282) 1991 (Box 56)
  - Amendments VCU 1992 (Box 56)
  - American Opportunities 1990 (Box 56)
  - Anatomical Gifts; Definitions (SB 779) 1989 (Box 56)
  - Architects and Engineers (SB 607) 1994 (Box 56)
  - Armed Career Criminals (SB 821) 1993 (Box 56)
  - Assaults by Juveniles on Correctional Officers and Teachers (SB 20) 1996 (Box 56)
  - Assaults on Teachers (SB 1167) 1997 (Box 56)
  - Assessment for Court Related facilities (SB 353) 1992 (Box 56)
  - BACL 1994 (Box 56)
  - Bail and Recognizance (SB 444) 1997 (Box 56)
  - Bail; Unsecured Bond (SB 444) 1996 (Box 56)
  - Benedetti Bills 1987-1996 (Box 56)
  - Benedetti Votes 1989 (Box 56)
  - Bills-Drafted-not introduced 1989, 1995 (Box 56)
  - Bills-list 1991 (Box 56)
  - Bills not filed 1992-1993, 1997 (Box 56)
  - Bill tracking 1997 (Box 56)
  - Bingo-Audits (SB 160) 1990 (Box 56)
  - Bingo-Games and Raffles (SB 745) 1989 (Box 56)
  - Bingo-Gross Receipts (SB 159) 1990 (Box 56)
  - Bingo (HJR 137) 1986 (Box 56)
  - Bocock, Elizabeth (HJR 166) 1986 (Box 56)
  - Bon Air Correctional Center 1995 (Box 56)
  - Bone Marrow (HB 240) 1994 (Box 56)
  - Bosher's Dam 1996 (Box 56)
  - Bosher's Dam Fish Ladder 1997 (Box 56)
  - Breast Feeding (HB 1188) 1994 (Box 56)
  - Budget Amendments-Fishways 1989 (Box 56)
  - Budget Amendments-Capital Improvements 1989 (Box 56)
  - Budget Amendments 1991-1997 (Box 56)
  - Budget Debates-Senate Floor 1995 (Box 56)
  - Budget Summaries 1992-1994 (Box 56)
  - Budget Talking Points 1995 (Box 56)
  - Business Tax Credits (SB 351) 1992 (Box 56)
  - Campaign-Attorney General 1991 (Box 56)
  - Campaign Contributions and Expenditures (SB 362) 1993 (Box 56)
  - Campaign Offenses (SB 284) 1992-1993 (Box 56)
  - Capital Review 1997 (Box 57)
  - Carry Overs (SB 20) 1996-1997 (Box 57)
  - Charitable Gaming (SB 916) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Chesapeake Bay Committee Progress Reports 1993 (Box 57)
  - Chief Patron Bills 1989-1993 (Box 57)
  - Chief Patron Reports 1986-1995 (Box 57)
  - Child Placement (HB 568) 1986 (Box 57)
  - Child and Spousal Support (SB 454) 1988 (Box 57)
  - Child Support Enforcement (SB 608) 1994 (Box 57)
  - Circuit Court Clerks Bill (HB 2579) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Clean Alternative Fuel 1993-1995 (Box 57)
  - Commending Coach Bobby Ross 1991 (Box 57)
  - Commending Coach Warren Rutledge (SJR 170) 1991 (Box 57)
  - Commending George Bush (SJR 232) 991 (Box 57)
  - Commending Imperial Plaza (SJR 286) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Commending Leslie Cheek, JR. (SJR 221) 1989 (Box 57)
  - Commending Mary Louise O'Conner Lucas (SR 5) 1994 (Box 57)
  - Commending Resolutions (SJR 130) 1987 (Box 57)
  - Commending Resolution-Citie of Henricus 1992 (Box 57)
  - Commending Retreat Hospital for Support 1992 (Box 57)
  - Commending the Richmond Jaycees 1991 (Box 57)
  - Commending ST. Gertrudes H.S. (SJR 150) 1996 (Box 57)
  - Committee Assignments Save for Archive 1996 (Box 57)
  - Committee on District Courts 1996 (Box 57)
  - Community Services Board (SB 351) 1988 (Box 57)
  - Concealed handgun Permit (SB 944) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Concealed Weapons (SB 156) 1990 (Box 57)
  - Concealed Weapons (SB 944) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Confederate Cemetery (HJ 601) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Conference Committee 1995 (Box 57)
  - Constituent Calls 1995 (Box 57)
  - Consumer Protection (SB 350) 1988 (Box 57)
  - Continuing Care (HB 455) 1986 (Box 57)
  - Contracts-Independent Sales Representative 1991 (Box 57)
  - Co-Patron Bills 1987, 1996 (Box 57)
  - Correspondence 1993, 1997 (Box 57)
  - County of Henrico 1996 (Box 57)
  - Courts not of record (SB 1170) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Crimes; Arson (SB 791) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Crimes; Possession of Arson Device (SB 794) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Crimes; Trespass on Church Property (SB 792) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Criminal Jurisdiction (SB 559) 1987 (Box 57)
  - Criminal Procedure (SB 918) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Criminal Records Check-Private Schools (SB 460) 1996 (Box 57)
  - Criminal Sentencing (SB 774) 1995 (Box 57)
  - Dams and Fishways (SB 456) 1988-1989 (Box 57)
  - Day Care-Family 1992 (Box 57)
  - Delinquet Tax Sale (SB 418) 1990 (Box 57)
  - Department of Economic Development Film Office (SB 343) 1994 (Box 57)
  - Deposit in Lieu of Bond (SB 349) 1988 (Box 57)
  - Design-Build Contracts 1987-1994 (Box 57)
  - Destruction-Old Warrants and Summonses (SB 878) 1993 (Box 57)
  - Dimethyl Sulfoxide 1996 (Box 57)
  - Disposition 1990 (Box 57)
  - Disney 1994 (Box 57)
  - Disney-Economic Development 1994 (Box 57)
  - Dissemination of Criminal History (SB 915) 1997 (Box 57)
  - Dismissal of Action (SB 770) 1995 (Box 57)
  - Driver's License Requirements 1994 (Box 57)
  - Driving Under Influence (SB 778) 1989 (Box 57)
  - Driving Under Influence (SB 406) 1990 (Box 57)
  - Drug and Alcohol Testing 1996 (Box 57)
  - Drug Court/Budget Amendment 1997 (Box 57)
  - Drug Free Zones (SB 776) 1991 (Box 57)
  - Election of Mayor-Richmond Charter (SB 635) 1996 (Box 58)
  - Employment Statistics 1996 (Box 58)
  - Establishing a Joint Subcommittee to study consolidation (SJ 116) 1994 (Box 58)
  - Exclusions from VA. Taxable Income 1989 (Box 58)
  - Exemptions from BPOL Taxes (SB 708) 1993 (Box 58)
  - Ex Parte Orders of Foreign Courts 1995 (Box 58)
  - Expense Accounts 1994 (Box 58)
  - Expungement of Police and Court Records 1992 (Box 58)
  - Fees Collected by Sheriffs 1995 (Box 58)